<projects>
	<project name="BlackCheck">
		<description>Except, a "blackjack" is the highest hand, consisting of an ace and any 10-point card, and it outranks all other 21-point hands. After the players have bet, the dealer will give two cards to each player and two cards to himself. One of the dealer cards is dealt face up. The facedown card is called the "hole card."</description>
		<images>
			<img name="thumbnail">bc/1.JPG</img>
			<img>bc/2.JPG</img>
			<img>bc/3.JPG</img>
			<img>bc/4.JPG</img>
			<img>bc/5.JPG</img>
		</images>
		
	</project>
	
	<project name="Memory-Game">
		<description>Concentration, also known as Match Match, Memory, Pelmanism, Shinkei-suijaku, Pexeso or simply Pairs, is a card game in which all of the cards are laid face down on a surface and two cards are flipped face up over each turn. The object of the game is to turn over pairs of matching cards.</description>
		<img>Memory-Game/1.JPG</img>
		<images>
			<img name="thumbnail">Memory-Game/2.JPG</img>
			<img>Memory-Game/3.JPG</img>
			<img>Memory-Game/4.JPG</img>
			<img>Memory-Game/5.JPG</img>
		</images>
		
	</project>
	
	<project name="Suduko">
		<description>Definition of sudoku. : a puzzle in which several numbers are to be filled into a 9x9 grid of squares so that every row, every column, and every 3x3 box contains the numbers 1 through 9.</description>
		<images>
			<img name="thumbnail">Suduko/2.JPG</img>
			<img>Suduko/3.JPG</img>
		
		</images>

	</project>
	
	<project name="Tic-Tac">
		<description>Tic-tac-toe (also known as noughts and crosses or Xs and Os) is a paper-and-pencil game for two players, X and O, who take turns marking the spaces in a 3×3 grid. The player who succeeds in placing three of their marks in a horizontal, vertical, or diagonal row wins the game.</description>
		<images>
			<img name="thumbnail">Tic-Tac/1.JPG</img>
		   <img>Tic-Tac/2.JPG</img>		
		</images>
		
	</project>
	
	<project name="Worlde">
		<description>A wordle is a visual depiction of the words contained in a piece of text, as exemplified within the citation above. Generated by a web-based tool of the same name, a wordle is created by manipulating the words of an input text and arranging them into a kind of graphic.</description>
		<images>
			<img name="thumbnail">Worlde/1.JPG</img>
			<img>Worlde/2.JPG</img>
			<img>Worlde/3.JPG</img>
	
		</images>
		
	</project>
	
</projects>